{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4092","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Blue Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Detroit 90/90","licenseNumber":"237185","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Non-Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"210","coords":"-83.07361,42.36260","geojson":{"id":"4092","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.073614691,42.36260391]},"properties":{"name":"University Prep Academy HS--Blue Bldg.","owner":"Detroit 90/90","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"237185","establishmentid":"4092","establishment_type":"Non-Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210","most_recent_license_date":"5/22/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622962","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Yellow Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622960","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Green Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622961","name":"University Prep Academy HS--Purple Bldg.","address":"600 Antoinette St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"612","name":"Cafe 1 - Henry Ford Health System","address":"1 Ford Place","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"3793","name":"University Preparatory Academy Elem","address":"435 Amsterdam St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"3518","name":"Jet's Pizza Midtown","address":"4718 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622602","name":"Harmony Garden Cafe'","address":"4704 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4216","name":"Harmoni Garden","address":"4704 Anthony Wayne Dr","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4093","name":"University Prep Academy Elementary","address":"957 Holden St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622990","name":"Wayne Co Mrkt, LLC dba Plum Mrkt (1stFl)","address":"6201 Second Ave","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49362","inspectionDate":"2019-10-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"47929","inspectionDate":"2019-05-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink(s)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42145","inspectionDate":"2018-04-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-202.11","violationDescription":"(A)  Refrigerated, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be at a temperature of 41째F or below when received, except as allowed by LAW.  POTENTIALLY             HAZARDOUS FOOD that is cooked and received hot shall be  at 135째F or             above. (P) \r\n(B)  A FOOD that is labeled frozen and shipped frozen by a FOOD PROCESSING     PLANT shall be received frozen. (Pf) \r\n(C)  Upon receipt, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be free of evidence of previous temperature abuse. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Received below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-04-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Return to supplier."}]},{"inspectionid":"41113","inspectionDate":"2017-12-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-202.11","violationDescription":"(A)  Refrigerated, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be at a temperature of 41째F or below when received, except as allowed by LAW.  POTENTIALLY             HAZARDOUS FOOD that is cooked and received hot shall be  at 135째F or             above. (P) \r\n(B)  A FOOD that is labeled frozen and shipped frozen by a FOOD PROCESSING     PLANT shall be received frozen. (Pf) \r\n(C)  Upon receipt, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be free of evidence of previous temperature abuse. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Hot food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Received below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-12-15T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Return to supplier."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"GREEN BUILDING","subLocation":"Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."}]},{"inspectionid":"39455","inspectionDate":"2017-06-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"STEAM TABLE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"sink","subItem":"handwash","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Throughout Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"BROKEN Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Throughout Three compartment sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."}]},{"inspectionid":"37169","inspectionDate":"2016-11-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"BLUE BUILDING","subLocation":"Cooler (milk)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"YELLOW BUILDING","subLocation":"Hot Holding Wells","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4092"}}